[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '呼びます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はなし"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '話します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "みせます"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '話し' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "はじめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '見せます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "おしえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '始めます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "じゅう, しょ"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '教えます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ふります"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '住所' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "なまえ"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '降ります' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "すぐ"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '名前' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しお"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '直ぐ' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "さとう"
    }
]
